[{"subjectID":"74pukc3mt2","prolificID":"57d37b8f677a440001b9f0c8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215cc3f3e97201972e78","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664065703,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"219","question":"What are some topics you find yourself drawn to (for example, the roman empire, medieval cat paintings) that aren’t related to other aspects of your life?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":14595,"timeElapsed":67820},{"subjectID":"74pukc3mt2","prolificID":"57d37b8f677a440001b9f0c8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215cc3f3e97201972e78","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664072683,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"219","question":"What are some topics you find yourself drawn to (for example, the roman empire, medieval cat paintings) that aren’t related to other aspects of your life?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":6977,"timeElapsed":74800},{"subjectID":"74pukc3mt2","prolificID":"57d37b8f677a440001b9f0c8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215cc3f3e97201972e78","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664077529,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"219","question":"What are some topics you find yourself drawn to (for example, the roman empire, medieval cat paintings) that aren’t related to other aspects of your life?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":4842,"timeElapsed":79646},{"subjectID":"74pukc3mt2","prolificID":"57d37b8f677a440001b9f0c8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215cc3f3e97201972e78","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664080103,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"219","question":"What are some topics you find yourself drawn to (for example, the roman empire, medieval cat paintings) that aren’t related to other aspects of your life?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":2568,"timeElapsed":82219},{"subjectID":"74pukc3mt2","prolificID":"57d37b8f677a440001b9f0c8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215cc3f3e97201972e78","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664082763,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"219","question":"What are some topics you find yourself drawn to (for example, the roman empire, medieval cat paintings) that aren’t related to other aspects of your life?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":2656,"timeElapsed":84880},{"subjectID":"74pukc3mt2","prolificID":"57d37b8f677a440001b9f0c8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215cc3f3e97201972e78","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664086724,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"219","question":"What are some topics you find yourself drawn to (for example, the roman empire, medieval cat paintings) that aren’t related to other aspects of your life?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":3955,"timeElapsed":88841},{"subjectID":"74pukc3mt2","prolificID":"57d37b8f677a440001b9f0c8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215cc3f3e97201972e78","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664088819,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"219","question":"What are some topics you find yourself drawn to (for example, the roman empire, medieval cat paintings) that aren’t related to other aspects of your life?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":2091,"timeElapsed":90936},{"subjectID":"74pukc3mt2","prolificID":"57d37b8f677a440001b9f0c8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215cc3f3e97201972e78","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664091731,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"219","question":"What are some topics you find yourself drawn to (for example, the roman empire, medieval cat paintings) that aren’t related to other aspects of your life?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":2905,"timeElapsed":93847},{"subjectID":"74pukc3mt2","prolificID":"57d37b8f677a440001b9f0c8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215cc3f3e97201972e78","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664093359,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"219","question":"What are some topics you find yourself drawn to (for example, the roman empire, medieval cat paintings) that aren’t related to other aspects of your life?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":1625,"timeElapsed":95476},{"subjectID":"74pukc3mt2","prolificID":"57d37b8f677a440001b9f0c8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215cc3f3e97201972e78","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664106444,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"148","question":"Say a word that comes to mind, then say the first word you can think of that starts with the last letter of the word you just said. Keep adding words that start with the last letter of the previous word until you have 25 words. Any words will do–you do not need to make a sentence.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":12171,"timeElapsed":108560},{"subjectID":"74pukc3mt2","prolificID":"57d37b8f677a440001b9f0c8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215cc3f3e97201972e78","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664108398,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"148","question":"Say a word that comes to mind, then say the first word you can think of that starts with the last letter of the word you just said. Keep adding words that start with the last letter of the previous word until you have 25 words. Any words will do–you do not need to make a sentence.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":88,"rt":1951,"timeElapsed":110515},{"subjectID":"74pukc3mt2","prolificID":"57d37b8f677a440001b9f0c8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215cc3f3e97201972e78","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664111081,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"148","question":"Say a word that comes to mind, then say the first word you can think of that starts with the last letter of the word you just said. Keep adding words that start with the last letter of the previous word until you have 25 words. Any words will do–you do not need to make a sentence.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":99,"rt":2679,"timeElapsed":113198},{"subjectID":"74pukc3mt2","prolificID":"57d37b8f677a440001b9f0c8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215cc3f3e97201972e78","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664114824,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"148","question":"Say a word that comes to mind, then say the first word you can think of that starts with the last letter of the word you just said. Keep adding words that start with the last letter of the previous word until you have 25 words. Any words will do–you do not need to make a sentence.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3737,"timeElapsed":116940},{"subjectID":"74pukc3mt2","prolificID":"57d37b8f677a440001b9f0c8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215cc3f3e97201972e78","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664117405,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"148","question":"Say a word that comes to mind, then say the first word you can think of that starts with the last letter of the word you just said. Keep adding words that start with the last letter of the previous word until you have 25 words. Any words will do–you do not need to make a sentence.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":90,"rt":2578,"timeElapsed":119522},{"subjectID":"74pukc3mt2","prolificID":"57d37b8f677a440001b9f0c8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215cc3f3e97201972e78","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664119272,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"148","question":"Say a word that comes to mind, then say the first word you can think of that starts with the last letter of the word you just said. Keep adding words that start with the last letter of the previous word until you have 25 words. Any words will do–you do not need to make a sentence.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":86,"rt":1863,"timeElapsed":121389},{"subjectID":"74pukc3mt2","prolificID":"57d37b8f677a440001b9f0c8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215cc3f3e97201972e78","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664120913,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"148","question":"Say a word that comes to mind, then say the first word you can think of that starts with the last letter of the word you just said. Keep adding words that start with the last letter of the previous word until you have 25 words. Any words will do–you do not need to make a sentence.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":89,"rt":1636,"timeElapsed":123030},{"subjectID":"74pukc3mt2","prolificID":"57d37b8f677a440001b9f0c8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215cc3f3e97201972e78","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664122570,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"148","question":"Say a word that comes to mind, then say the first word you can think of that starts with the last letter of the word you just said. Keep adding words that start with the last letter of the previous word until you have 25 words. Any words will do–you do not need to make a sentence.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":86,"rt":1653,"timeElapsed":124687},{"subjectID":"74pukc3mt2","prolificID":"57d37b8f677a440001b9f0c8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215cc3f3e97201972e78","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664126233,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"148","question":"Say a word that comes to mind, then say the first word you can think of that starts with the last letter of the word you just said. Keep adding words that start with the last letter of the previous word until you have 25 words. Any words will do–you do not need to make a sentence.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":84,"rt":3657,"timeElapsed":128350},{"subjectID":"74pukc3mt2","prolificID":"57d37b8f677a440001b9f0c8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215cc3f3e97201972e78","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664130986,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"54","question":"Do you believe in the death penalty? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3607,"timeElapsed":133103},{"subjectID":"74pukc3mt2","prolificID":"57d37b8f677a440001b9f0c8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215cc3f3e97201972e78","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664132434,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"54","question":"Do you believe in the death penalty? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":1444,"timeElapsed":134551},{"subjectID":"74pukc3mt2","prolificID":"57d37b8f677a440001b9f0c8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215cc3f3e97201972e78","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664134012,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"54","question":"Do you believe in the death penalty? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":1574,"timeElapsed":136128},{"subjectID":"74pukc3mt2","prolificID":"57d37b8f677a440001b9f0c8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215cc3f3e97201972e78","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664135567,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"54","question":"Do you believe in the death penalty? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":1549,"timeElapsed":137684},{"subjectID":"74pukc3mt2","prolificID":"57d37b8f677a440001b9f0c8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215cc3f3e97201972e78","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664137154,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"54","question":"Do you believe in the death penalty? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":1584,"timeElapsed":139271},{"subjectID":"74pukc3mt2","prolificID":"57d37b8f677a440001b9f0c8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215cc3f3e97201972e78","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664142066,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"54","question":"Do you believe in the death penalty? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":4909,"timeElapsed":144183},{"subjectID":"74pukc3mt2","prolificID":"57d37b8f677a440001b9f0c8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215cc3f3e97201972e78","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664143865,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"54","question":"Do you believe in the death penalty? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":1794,"timeElapsed":145982},{"subjectID":"74pukc3mt2","prolificID":"57d37b8f677a440001b9f0c8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215cc3f3e97201972e78","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664145915,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"54","question":"Do you believe in the death penalty? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2045,"timeElapsed":148031},{"subjectID":"74pukc3mt2","prolificID":"57d37b8f677a440001b9f0c8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215cc3f3e97201972e78","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664147514,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"54","question":"Do you believe in the death penalty? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":1594,"timeElapsed":149631},{"subjectID":"74pukc3mt2","prolificID":"57d37b8f677a440001b9f0c8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215cc3f3e97201972e78","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664151471,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"225","question":"If you won the lottery, what is the first thing you would do?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3017,"timeElapsed":153588},{"subjectID":"74pukc3mt2","prolificID":"57d37b8f677a440001b9f0c8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215cc3f3e97201972e78","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664152737,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"225","question":"If you won the lottery, what is the first thing you would do?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":98,"rt":1264,"timeElapsed":154854},{"subjectID":"74pukc3mt2","prolificID":"57d37b8f677a440001b9f0c8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215cc3f3e97201972e78","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664154033,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"225","question":"If you won the lottery, what is the first thing you would do?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":1293,"timeElapsed":156150},{"subjectID":"74pukc3mt2","prolificID":"57d37b8f677a440001b9f0c8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215cc3f3e97201972e78","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664155364,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"225","question":"If you won the lottery, what is the first thing you would do?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":1327,"timeElapsed":157481},{"subjectID":"74pukc3mt2","prolificID":"57d37b8f677a440001b9f0c8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215cc3f3e97201972e78","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664156701,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"225","question":"If you won the lottery, what is the first thing you would do?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":1334,"timeElapsed":158818},{"subjectID":"74pukc3mt2","prolificID":"57d37b8f677a440001b9f0c8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215cc3f3e97201972e78","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664158046,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"225","question":"If you won the lottery, what is the first thing you would do?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":1342,"timeElapsed":160163},{"subjectID":"74pukc3mt2","prolificID":"57d37b8f677a440001b9f0c8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215cc3f3e97201972e78","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664159345,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"225","question":"If you won the lottery, what is the first thing you would do?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":1296,"timeElapsed":161461},{"subjectID":"74pukc3mt2","prolificID":"57d37b8f677a440001b9f0c8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215cc3f3e97201972e78","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664161340,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"225","question":"If you won the lottery, what is the first thing you would do?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":1993,"timeElapsed":163457},{"subjectID":"74pukc3mt2","prolificID":"57d37b8f677a440001b9f0c8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215cc3f3e97201972e78","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664163293,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"225","question":"If you won the lottery, what is the first thing you would do?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":1950,"timeElapsed":165410},{"subjectID":"74pukc3mt2","prolificID":"57d37b8f677a440001b9f0c8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215cc3f3e97201972e78","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664168382,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"175","question":"Do you have a default pizza order? What is it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":85,"rt":4161,"timeElapsed":170499},{"subjectID":"74pukc3mt2","prolificID":"57d37b8f677a440001b9f0c8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215cc3f3e97201972e78","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664169701,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"175","question":"Do you have a default pizza order? What is it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":84,"rt":1316,"timeElapsed":171818},{"subjectID":"74pukc3mt2","prolificID":"57d37b8f677a440001b9f0c8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215cc3f3e97201972e78","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664170980,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"175","question":"Do you have a default pizza order? What is it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":83,"rt":1276,"timeElapsed":173097},{"subjectID":"74pukc3mt2","prolificID":"57d37b8f677a440001b9f0c8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215cc3f3e97201972e78","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664172723,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"175","question":"Do you have a default pizza order? What is it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":29,"rt":1739,"timeElapsed":174839},{"subjectID":"74pukc3mt2","prolificID":"57d37b8f677a440001b9f0c8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215cc3f3e97201972e78","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664176608,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"Do you have a default pizza order? What is it?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3881,"timeElapsed":178725},{"subjectID":"74pukc3mt2","prolificID":"57d37b8f677a440001b9f0c8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215cc3f3e97201972e78","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664178646,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"175","question":"Do you have a default pizza order? What is it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":2034,"timeElapsed":180763},{"subjectID":"74pukc3mt2","prolificID":"57d37b8f677a440001b9f0c8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215cc3f3e97201972e78","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664180911,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"175","question":"Do you have a default pizza order? What is it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":51,"rt":2262,"timeElapsed":183028},{"subjectID":"74pukc3mt2","prolificID":"57d37b8f677a440001b9f0c8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215cc3f3e97201972e78","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664182199,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"175","question":"Do you have a default pizza order? What is it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":1285,"timeElapsed":184316},{"subjectID":"74pukc3mt2","prolificID":"57d37b8f677a440001b9f0c8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215cc3f3e97201972e78","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664183502,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"175","question":"Do you have a default pizza order? What is it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":43,"rt":1300,"timeElapsed":185619},{"subjectID":"74pukc3mt2","prolificID":"57d37b8f677a440001b9f0c8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215cc3f3e97201972e78","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664184503,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"175","question":"Do you have a default pizza order? What is it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":997,"timeElapsed":186620},{"subjectID":"74pukc3mt2","prolificID":"57d37b8f677a440001b9f0c8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215cc3f3e97201972e78","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664188106,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"27","question":"Describe an embarrassing moment in your life.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2877,"timeElapsed":190223},{"subjectID":"74pukc3mt2","prolificID":"57d37b8f677a440001b9f0c8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215cc3f3e97201972e78","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664189335,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"27","question":"Describe an embarrassing moment in your life.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":1225,"timeElapsed":191452},{"subjectID":"74pukc3mt2","prolificID":"57d37b8f677a440001b9f0c8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215cc3f3e97201972e78","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664190560,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"27","question":"Describe an embarrassing moment in your life.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":99,"rt":1220,"timeElapsed":192676},{"subjectID":"74pukc3mt2","prolificID":"57d37b8f677a440001b9f0c8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215cc3f3e97201972e78","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664191712,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"27","question":"Describe an embarrassing moment in your life.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":1148,"timeElapsed":193829},{"subjectID":"74pukc3mt2","prolificID":"57d37b8f677a440001b9f0c8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215cc3f3e97201972e78","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664192962,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"27","question":"Describe an embarrassing moment in your life.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":1246,"timeElapsed":195079},{"subjectID":"74pukc3mt2","prolificID":"57d37b8f677a440001b9f0c8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215cc3f3e97201972e78","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664194407,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"27","question":"Describe an embarrassing moment in your life.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":1442,"timeElapsed":196524},{"subjectID":"74pukc3mt2","prolificID":"57d37b8f677a440001b9f0c8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215cc3f3e97201972e78","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664195657,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"27","question":"Describe an embarrassing moment in your life.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":1245,"timeElapsed":197773},{"subjectID":"74pukc3mt2","prolificID":"57d37b8f677a440001b9f0c8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215cc3f3e97201972e78","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664196925,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"27","question":"Describe an embarrassing moment in your life.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":1265,"timeElapsed":199042},{"subjectID":"74pukc3mt2","prolificID":"57d37b8f677a440001b9f0c8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215cc3f3e97201972e78","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664198198,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"27","question":"Describe an embarrassing moment in your life.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":1269,"timeElapsed":200314},{"subjectID":"74pukc3mt2","prolificID":"57d37b8f677a440001b9f0c8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215cc3f3e97201972e78","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664201670,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"48","question":"Do you believe in fate or destiny? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2615,"timeElapsed":203787},{"subjectID":"74pukc3mt2","prolificID":"57d37b8f677a440001b9f0c8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215cc3f3e97201972e78","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664202901,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"48","question":"Do you believe in fate or destiny? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":99,"rt":1228,"timeElapsed":205018},{"subjectID":"74pukc3mt2","prolificID":"57d37b8f677a440001b9f0c8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215cc3f3e97201972e78","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664204156,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"48","question":"Do you believe in fate or destiny? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":1253,"timeElapsed":206273},{"subjectID":"74pukc3mt2","prolificID":"57d37b8f677a440001b9f0c8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215cc3f3e97201972e78","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664205218,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"48","question":"Do you believe in fate or destiny? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":1059,"timeElapsed":207335},{"subjectID":"74pukc3mt2","prolificID":"57d37b8f677a440001b9f0c8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215cc3f3e97201972e78","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664206400,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"48","question":"Do you believe in fate or destiny? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":1179,"timeElapsed":208517},{"subjectID":"74pukc3mt2","prolificID":"57d37b8f677a440001b9f0c8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215cc3f3e97201972e78","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664207742,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"48","question":"Do you believe in fate or destiny? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":1338,"timeElapsed":209859},{"subjectID":"74pukc3mt2","prolificID":"57d37b8f677a440001b9f0c8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215cc3f3e97201972e78","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664208900,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"48","question":"Do you believe in fate or destiny? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":1155,"timeElapsed":211016},{"subjectID":"74pukc3mt2","prolificID":"57d37b8f677a440001b9f0c8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215cc3f3e97201972e78","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664210127,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"48","question":"Do you believe in fate or destiny? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":1224,"timeElapsed":212244},{"subjectID":"74pukc3mt2","prolificID":"57d37b8f677a440001b9f0c8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215cc3f3e97201972e78","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664211393,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"48","question":"Do you believe in fate or destiny? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":1263,"timeElapsed":213510},{"subjectID":"74pukc3mt2","prolificID":"57d37b8f677a440001b9f0c8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215cc3f3e97201972e78","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664215616,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"129","question":"When you think about the future, what do you most think about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3351,"timeElapsed":217733},{"subjectID":"74pukc3mt2","prolificID":"57d37b8f677a440001b9f0c8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215cc3f3e97201972e78","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664216756,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"129","question":"When you think about the future, what do you most think about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":1136,"timeElapsed":218873},{"subjectID":"74pukc3mt2","prolificID":"57d37b8f677a440001b9f0c8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215cc3f3e97201972e78","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664217930,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"129","question":"When you think about the future, what do you most think about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":1169,"timeElapsed":220047},{"subjectID":"74pukc3mt2","prolificID":"57d37b8f677a440001b9f0c8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215cc3f3e97201972e78","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664219644,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"129","question":"When you think about the future, what do you most think about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":1708,"timeElapsed":221760},{"subjectID":"74pukc3mt2","prolificID":"57d37b8f677a440001b9f0c8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215cc3f3e97201972e78","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664221001,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"129","question":"When you think about the future, what do you most think about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":1351,"timeElapsed":223118},{"subjectID":"74pukc3mt2","prolificID":"57d37b8f677a440001b9f0c8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215cc3f3e97201972e78","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664223364,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"129","question":"When you think about the future, what do you most think about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2359,"timeElapsed":225481},{"subjectID":"74pukc3mt2","prolificID":"57d37b8f677a440001b9f0c8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215cc3f3e97201972e78","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664226362,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"When you think about the future, what do you most think about?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2995,"timeElapsed":228479},{"subjectID":"74pukc3mt2","prolificID":"57d37b8f677a440001b9f0c8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215cc3f3e97201972e78","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664228169,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"129","question":"When you think about the future, what do you most think about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":1803,"timeElapsed":230286},{"subjectID":"74pukc3mt2","prolificID":"57d37b8f677a440001b9f0c8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215cc3f3e97201972e78","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664229566,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"129","question":"When you think about the future, what do you most think about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":1392,"timeElapsed":231683},{"subjectID":"74pukc3mt2","prolificID":"57d37b8f677a440001b9f0c8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215cc3f3e97201972e78","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664231722,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"129","question":"When you think about the future, what do you most think about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2152,"timeElapsed":233839},{"subjectID":"74pukc3mt2","prolificID":"57d37b8f677a440001b9f0c8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215cc3f3e97201972e78","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664238415,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"176","question":"What is your strategy for eating a really messy taco?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":1,"rt":5805,"timeElapsed":240532},{"subjectID":"74pukc3mt2","prolificID":"57d37b8f677a440001b9f0c8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215cc3f3e97201972e78","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664239821,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"176","question":"What is your strategy for eating a really messy taco?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":6,"rt":1402,"timeElapsed":241938},{"subjectID":"74pukc3mt2","prolificID":"57d37b8f677a440001b9f0c8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215cc3f3e97201972e78","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664241270,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"176","question":"What is your strategy for eating a really messy taco?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":9,"rt":1444,"timeElapsed":243387},{"subjectID":"74pukc3mt2","prolificID":"57d37b8f677a440001b9f0c8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215cc3f3e97201972e78","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664242692,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"176","question":"What is your strategy for eating a really messy taco?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":1,"rt":1417,"timeElapsed":244809},{"subjectID":"74pukc3mt2","prolificID":"57d37b8f677a440001b9f0c8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215cc3f3e97201972e78","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664244176,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"176","question":"What is your strategy for eating a really messy taco?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":1479,"timeElapsed":246293},{"subjectID":"74pukc3mt2","prolificID":"57d37b8f677a440001b9f0c8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215cc3f3e97201972e78","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664245951,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"176","question":"What is your strategy for eating a really messy taco?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":1,"rt":1770,"timeElapsed":248067},{"subjectID":"74pukc3mt2","prolificID":"57d37b8f677a440001b9f0c8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215cc3f3e97201972e78","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664247254,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"176","question":"What is your strategy for eating a really messy taco?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":1298,"timeElapsed":249371},{"subjectID":"74pukc3mt2","prolificID":"57d37b8f677a440001b9f0c8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215cc3f3e97201972e78","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664248734,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"176","question":"What is your strategy for eating a really messy taco?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":1476,"timeElapsed":250851},{"subjectID":"74pukc3mt2","prolificID":"57d37b8f677a440001b9f0c8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215cc3f3e97201972e78","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664250227,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"176","question":"What is your strategy for eating a really messy taco?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":1490,"timeElapsed":252344},{"subjectID":"74pukc3mt2","prolificID":"57d37b8f677a440001b9f0c8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215cc3f3e97201972e78","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664254374,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"57","question":"Do you think your children (or the next generation of children) will inherit a world that is overall better than the current one or worse? In what ways will the future be better or worse?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3342,"timeElapsed":256491},{"subjectID":"74pukc3mt2","prolificID":"57d37b8f677a440001b9f0c8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215cc3f3e97201972e78","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664255780,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"57","question":"Do you think your children (or the next generation of children) will inherit a world that is overall better than the current one or worse? In what ways will the future be better or worse?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":1399,"timeElapsed":257897},{"subjectID":"74pukc3mt2","prolificID":"57d37b8f677a440001b9f0c8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215cc3f3e97201972e78","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664257147,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"57","question":"Do you think your children (or the next generation of children) will inherit a world that is overall better than the current one or worse? In what ways will the future be better or worse?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":1363,"timeElapsed":259263},{"subjectID":"74pukc3mt2","prolificID":"57d37b8f677a440001b9f0c8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215cc3f3e97201972e78","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664258301,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"57","question":"Do you think your children (or the next generation of children) will inherit a world that is overall better than the current one or worse? In what ways will the future be better or worse?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":1151,"timeElapsed":260418},{"subjectID":"74pukc3mt2","prolificID":"57d37b8f677a440001b9f0c8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215cc3f3e97201972e78","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664259521,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"57","question":"Do you think your children (or the next generation of children) will inherit a world that is overall better than the current one or worse? In what ways will the future be better or worse?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":1216,"timeElapsed":261638},{"subjectID":"74pukc3mt2","prolificID":"57d37b8f677a440001b9f0c8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215cc3f3e97201972e78","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664260929,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"57","question":"Do you think your children (or the next generation of children) will inherit a world that is overall better than the current one or worse? In what ways will the future be better or worse?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":1402,"timeElapsed":263046},{"subjectID":"74pukc3mt2","prolificID":"57d37b8f677a440001b9f0c8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215cc3f3e97201972e78","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664262140,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"57","question":"Do you think your children (or the next generation of children) will inherit a world that is overall better than the current one or worse? In what ways will the future be better or worse?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":1205,"timeElapsed":264257},{"subjectID":"74pukc3mt2","prolificID":"57d37b8f677a440001b9f0c8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215cc3f3e97201972e78","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664263592,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"57","question":"Do you think your children (or the next generation of children) will inherit a world that is overall better than the current one or worse? In what ways will the future be better or worse?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":1447,"timeElapsed":265709},{"subjectID":"74pukc3mt2","prolificID":"57d37b8f677a440001b9f0c8","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215cc3f3e97201972e78","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664265000,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"57","question":"Do you think your children (or the next generation of children) will inherit a world that is overall better than the current one or worse? In what ways will the future be better or worse?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":1404,"timeElapsed":267117}]